export default data = [
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'cat'?",
    options: ["/kæt/", "/kɪt/", "/kat/", "/kɑt/"],
    correct_option: "/kæt/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'three'?",
    options: ["/θri/", "/θriː/", "/tri/", "/triː/"],
    correct_option: "/θriː/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'happy'?",
    options: ["/hæpi/", "/hapi/", "/hepi/", "/hɑpi/"],
    correct_option: "/hæpi/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'tree'?",
    options: ["/tri/", "/tɹi/", "/tɹiː/", "/tre/"],
    correct_option: "/tɹiː/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'bag'?",
    options: ["/bæɡ/", "/bæi/", "/bɔɡ/", "/bɪɡ/"],
    correct_option: "/bæɡ/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'goose'?",
    options: ["/ɡus/", "/ɡuːs/", "/ɡuz/", "/ɡuːz/"],
    correct_option: "/ɡuːs/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'sheep'?",
    options: ["/ʃip/", "/ʃiːp/", "/ʃep/", "/ʃiːb/"],
    correct_option: "/ʃiːp/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'love'?",
    options: ["/lʌv/", "/lʊv/", "/lɔv/", "/luv/"],
    correct_option: "/luv/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'big'?",
    options: ["/bɪɡ/", "/bɑɡ/", "/biɡ/", "/beɡ/"],
    correct_option: "/bɪɡ/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'juice'?",
    options: ["/dʒus/", "/dʒuːs/", "/dʒuz/", "/dʒuːz/"],
    correct_option: "/dʒuːs/",
  },
];
